- Where we look at what concerns that agriculture causes with -
- In the form of emissions of fertilizing substances and if we can avoid it in different ways.
When it comes to these eutrophic substances, there are a lot -
- A whole battery of various measures that can be taken.
- Since then we have looked at this with peatlands -
- For peatlands has proven to be a very large greenhouse gas emissions.
Can we return these peatlands so that they become wetlands again -
–And then harvest the material that grows up, for example, reed -
- And use it for biogas, so we get a double climate benefit.
I have been doing plants -
–And I have been dealing with environmental issues in different places -